Guide to the Records of Amnesty International of the USA, Inc.
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VII: Campaign and Country Files, 1972-1997
  - Subseries VII.3: Other Campaigns and Supporting Files, 1979-1995
    - Women's Campaigns and Supporting Files, 1982-1995
      - Prisoners-- Through the Wire, 1990 (Box 354, Folder 21)
        (film re women at Lexington Federal Prison)
      - Refugees--General, 1988-1993, (3 Folders) (Box 354, Folder 22-24)
      - United Nations--Fourth World Conference on Women (Beijing), 1995 September (Box 354, Folder 25)
      - Unfiled/Loose (Box 354, Folder 26)
      - Writers and Journalists Action, 1992 (Box 354, Folder 27)
- Series VIII: Closed Cases, 1974-1983
  ACCESS TO THE CASE FILES IN THIS RECORD GROUP IS RESTRICTED FOR 75 YEARS.
  These records consist of case files for released prisoners of conscience. The files include communications between Amnesty International offices and local groups, dossiers, guidelines, and reports on case activities from local groups. Some files also include correspondence generated and received by the local groups in the course of their work on cases.
  From 1975-1978, case files were assigned numbers and filed chronologically. After 1978, closed case files were filed by region and then alphabetically by country and surname. There are two sets of these alphabetical files - the main set, and a smaller second set that is filed in the last two boxes. When known, the number of the local group responsible for the case is identified in the finding aid. Several files were labeled as "good quote cases” and may have been used as material for publication or publicity efforts.
  In general, additional information on cases would be found in office files on local groups, and within the records of both local groups and country coordination groups.
  - A.I. Casework 'Success' Stories, (compiled by Bruce Hayes, intern--contains 15 cases) (Box 418, Folder 1)
  - Cases, 1974-1979 (Box 285)
    - #1-63, 1974-1976, (7 Folders) (Box 285, Folder 1-7)
    - #64-160, 1977, (13 Folders) (Box 285, Folder 8-20)
    - #161-287, 1978, (33 Folders) (Box 285, Folder 21-43)
    - #288-321,1978, (9 folders) (Box Box 286, Folder 1-9)
    - #322-#400,1979, (21 FOLDERS) (Box Box 286, Folder 10-30)
  - Closed Cases by Country (A number of these files were originally labeled "good quote cases," and the folders are marked as such),1979-1983
    - Africa
      - Benin
        - Adigbe, Etienne--USA# 299 (Box Box 286, Folder 31)
        - Adjotin, Pierre--USA# 198 (Box Box 286, Folder 32)
        - Afouda, Fulgence--USA# 50 (Box Box 286, Folder 33)
        - Agboton, Raphael--USA #77 (Box Box 286, Folder 34)
        - Ahouansou, Cyrille--USA #196 (Box Box 286, Folder 35)
        - Ale, Gregoire--USA #282 (Box Box 286, Folder 36)
        - Coffie, Andre Assou--USA# 248 (Box Box 286, Folder 37)
        - Djossou, Joseph--USA# 141 (Box Box 286, Folder 38)
        - Martin, Zacharie--USA #52 (Box Box 286, Folder 39)
        - Yelome, Leon--USA #154 (Box Box 286, Folder 40)
        - Case Closure Notices (Box Box 286, Folder 41)
      - Burkina Faso
        - Kindo, Ousmane Ismael--USA #21 (Box Box 286, Folder 42)
      - Burundi
        - Tharcisse, Rutumo--USA #263 (Box Box 286, Folder 43)
      - Cameroon
        - Niat, Marcel Njifenji--USA #77 (Box Box 286, Folder 44)
        - Nteh, Vincent--USA #283 (Box Box 286, Folder 45)
      - Central African Republic
        - Bozanga, Simon--USA# 280 (Box Box 286, Folder 46)
        - Dobozendi, Hugues--USA# 147 (Box Box 286, Folder 47)
        - Mangue, Michel--USA #156 (Box Box 286, Folder 48)
        - Saulet, Hubert (Box Box 286, Folder 49)
        - Case Closure Notices (Box Box 286, Folder 50)
      - Chad
        - Djourab, Moustapha Abbas--USA #294 (Box Box 286, Folder 51)
        - Chaibou, Ismail--USA #91 (Box Box 286, Folder 52)
        - Mohamen, El-Hadj--USA #263 (Box Box 286, Folder 53)
      - Comoros
        - Kassim, Ahmed (Box Box 286, Folder 54)
        - Madi, M’rouili (“Changani”) (Box Box 286, Folder 55)
      - Congo
        - Madimba, Eugene--USA# 67 (Box Box 286, Folder 56)
        - Case Closure Notices (Box Box 286, Folder 57)
      - Ethiopia
        - Kebede, Kongit--USA# 48 (Box Box 287, Folder 1)
        - Mariam, Kassa Wolde--USA #45 (Box Box 287, Folder 2)
        - Mesfin, Hirut--USA # 18 (Box Box 287, Folder 3)
        - Tewoflos, Bishop Abuna--USA #56 (Box Box 287, Folder 4)
        - Case Closure Notices (Box Box 287, Folder 5)
      - Gabon
        - Ndong, Samuel Ella--USA# 284 (Box Box 287, Folder 6)
        - Nguema, Jean-Pierre Nzoghe--USA# 242 (Box Box 287, Folder 7)
        - Nguimbi, Jerome--USA# 80 (Box Box 287, Folder 8)
        - Nziengui, Moubamba--USA# 205 (Box Box 287, Folder 9)
        - Ollomo, Luc Mue--USA# 278 (Box Box 287, Folder 10)
      - Ghana (Box Box 287, Folder 11)
      - Guinea
        - Camp Boiro--USA# 94 (Box Box 287, Folder 12)
        - Mady, Kaba Amiata--USA #94 (Box Box 287, Folder 13)
        - Adboulaye, Thiam--USA #156 (Box Box 287, Folder 14)
      - Kenya
        - Mazrui, Al-Amin Mohammed Kassim--USA# 23 (Box Box 287, Folder 15)
        - Otieno, Alfred Vincent--USA# 272 (Box Box 287, Folder 16)
      - Madagascar
        - Rakoto-Abel, Jean Astier--USA# 222 (Box Box 287, Folder 17)
        - Rakotondrauelo, Solo (Box Box 287, Folder 18)
      - Mali
        - Ba, Abdoul Gatta--USA# 42 (Box Box 287, Folder 19)
        - Ballo-Traore (Box Box 287, Folder 20)
      - Mauritania
        - Enahwi, Khalil Ould--USA# 31 (Box Box 287, Folder 21)
        - Lagdaf, Baham Ould Mohamed--USA# 15 (Box Box 287, Folder 22)
        - El Mani, Oumar Ould--USA# 18 (Box Box 287, Folder 23)
      - Mozambique
        - Goncalves, Pedro Jose--USA# 233 (Box Box 287, Folder 24)
      - Namibia
        - Goliath, Stefanus--USA# 83 (Box Box 287, Folder 25)
        - Hamutenya, Immanuel--USA# 81 (Box Box 287, Folder 26)
        - Hango, Simon--USA# 117 (Box Box 287, Folder 27)
        - Hangula, Simon--USA# 286 (Box Box 287, Folder 28)
        - Hauwanga, Eino--USA# 65 (Box Box 287, Folder 29)
        - Hidulika, Joseph--USA# 287 (Box Box 287, Folder 30)
        - Iikango, Leevi--USA# 165 (Box Box 287, Folder 31)
        - Iithete, Lazarus--USA# 244 (Box Box 287, Folder 32)
        - Kangaji, Jaakko--USA# 294 (Box Box 287, Folder 33)
        - Kaure, Adolf--USA# 171 (Box Box 287, Folder 34)
        - Matias, Louisa--USA# 254 (Box Box 287, Folder 35)
        - Nahole, Linus--USA# 27 (Box Box 287, Folder 36)
        - Nambala, Abner--USA# 178 (Box Box 287, Folder 37)
        - Nestor, Gideon--USA# 274 (Box Box 287, Folder 38)
        - Pickering, Arthur--USA# 150 (Box Box 287, Folder 39)
        - Shikongo, Franciscus--USA# 188 (Box Box 287, Folder 40)
        - Tobias, Philippus--USA# 15 (Box Box 287, Folder 41)
        - Case Closure Notices (Box Box 287, Folder 42)
      - Niger
        - Gaoh, Abdou--USA# 19 (Box Box 287, Folder 43)
        - Ibo, Abdou--USA# 294 (Box Box 287, Folder 44)
      - Nigeria
        - Adamu, Mallam Haroun (Box Box 287, Folder 45)
        - Ejiofor, Chigozie--USA# 273 (Box Box 287, Folder 46)
        - Rufai, Ibrahim--USA# 264 (Box Box 287, Folder 47)
      - Rwanda
        - Said, Habumugisha--USA# 138 (Box Box 287, Folder 48)
        - Maniraguha, Jacques--USA# 190 (Box Box 287, Folder 49)
        - Nazaire, Sarambuye--USA# 26 (Box Box 287, Folder 50)
        - Case Closure Notices (Box Box 287, Folder 51)
      - Sao Tome
        - Mendonca, Adelino--USA# 139 (Box Box 287, Folder 52)
      - Sierra Leone
        - Kpukuma, J.P. and 45 Others--USA# 121 (Box Box 287, Folder 53)
        - Tache-Qure, Andrew Fasuluku--USA# 37 (Box Box 287, Folder 54)
      - Somalia
        - Ali, Abdullah Farah--USA# 126 (Box Box 287, Folder 55)
        - Ali, Sheikh Ali--USA# 149 (Box Box 287, Folder 56)
        - Bogor, Mohamed Said--USA# 163 (Box Box 287, Folder 57)
        - Elma, Saida Botan--USA# 291 (Box Box 287, Folder 58)
        - Warsame and Weirah (Box Box 287, Folder 59)
        - Case Closure Notices (Box Box 287, Folder 60)
      - South Africa
        - Badela (Box Box 287, Folder 61)
        - Baliso-Booyren (Box Box 287, Folder 62)
        - Chikane, Reverend Frank--USA# 34 and 84 (Box Box 287, Folder 63)
        - Dikgole-Drew (Box Box 287, Folder 64)
        - Dunjwa, Mangexi--USA# 78 (Box Box 287, Folder 65)
        - Dyakala, Thamsanga--USA# 134 (Box Box 287, Folder 66)
        - Fani, Harrison--USA# 26 (Box Box 287, Folder 67)
        - Fantsi-Fazi (Box Box 287, Folder 68)
        - Finda, Sipho--USA# 273 (Box Box 287, Folder 69)
        - Gana, Jake--USA# 244 (Box Box 287, Folder 70)
        - Gasela-Gordhan (Box Box 287, Folder 71)
        - Gqueta, Thozamile--USA# 109 (Box Box 289, Folder 1)
        - Green-Huskie (Box Box 289, Folder 2)
        - Jola-Khumalo (Box Box 289, Folder 3)
        - Kiewits-Lesotho (Box Box 289, Folder 4)
        - Letsaba-Mabuza (Box Box 289, Folder 5)
        - Mackwana-Makelani (Box Box 289, Folder 6)
        - Makhathini-Maki (Box Box 289, Folder 7)
        - Makinana, Richard--USA# 113 (Box Box 289, Folder 8)
        - Makuza-Mankungu (Box Box 289, Folder 9)
        - Manzi-Mathonsi (Box Box 289, Folder 10)
        - Mathaopane-Matutu (Box Box 289, Folder 11)
        - Mazibuko, Fanyana--USA# 29 (Box Box 289, Folder 12)
        - Mazwai, Thami--USA# 168 (Box Box 289, Folder 13)
        - Mazongo-Mbelini (Box Box 289, Folder 14)
        - Mbepo-Mda (Box Box 289, Folder 15)
        - Mdleleni, Horatius--USA# 83 (Box Box 289, Folder 16)
        - Metele-Mlameni (Box Box 289, Folder 17)
        - Mni-Molekane (Box Box 289, Folder 18)
        - Moleko, Marks--USA# 13 (Box Box 289, Folder 19)
        - Molopeng-Mosibudu (Box Box 289, Folder 20)
        - Motha, Ida--USA# 10 (Box Box 289, Folder 21)
        - Motlaung-Mpumlwana (Box Box 289, Folder 22)
        - Mtimkulu, Phil--USA# 211 (Box Box 289, Folder 23)
        - Ntshekang, Motidi--USA# 90 (Box Box 289, Folder 24)
        - Mishingane-Nganzi (Box Box 289, Folder 25)
        - Ngcobo-Ngcuka (Box Box 289, Folder 26)
        - Ngqumba-Nhlabantsi (Box Box 289, Folder 27)
        - Njikelana, Sisa--USA# 239 (Box Box 289, Folder 28)
        - Nkodi-Ndabeni (Box Box 289, Folder 29)
        - Nontsele, Mncedisi--USA# 161 (Box Box 289, Folder 30)
        - Nontsile-Pharasi (Box Box 289, Folder 31)
        - Phungula, Helia--USA# 225 (Box Box 289, Folder 32)
        - Pillay-Rhodes (Box Box 289, Folder 33)
        - Roji, Skenjane--USA# 122 (Box Box 289, Folder 34)
        - Shezi-Slotile (Box Box 289, Folder 35)
        - Sondlo, Liyanda--USA# 39 (Box Box 289, Folder 36)
        - Sotaka-Thaver (Box Box 289, Folder 37)
        - Thuntsi, Arthur Mafisto--USA# 98 (Box Box 289, Folder 38)
        - Tom-Tsoktsi (Box Box 289, Folder 39)
        - Vandeyar, Reggie Pakiry--USA# 3/16 (Box Box 290, Folder 1)
        - Vilakazi-Xobololo (Box Box 290, Folder 2)
        - Yamile-Yeats (Box Box 290, Folder 3)
        - Yekwa-Zondo (Box Box 290, Folder 4)
        - Unfiled Case Closure Sheets (Box Box 290, Folder 5)
      - Sudan
        - Akashk-El Dahab (Box Box 290, Folder 6)
        - El Eaddal-El Magdrub (Box Box 290, Folder 7)
        - El Mahdi, Sadiq--USA# 21 (Box Box 290, Folder 8)
        - El Malik-Israhim (Box Box 290, Folder 9)
        - Mdut-Mahmoud (Box Box 290, Folder 10)
        - Marhal, Abuzman--USA# 31 (Box Box 290, Folder 11)
        - Mekki-Mohamed (Box Box 290, Folder 12)
        - Mohi, Ismail-Eldin Rasikh--USA# 119 (Box Box 290, Folder 13)
        - Saeed, Dr. El Shafi Khidir--USA# 151 (Box Box 290, Folder 14)
        - Siddig-Tom (Box Box 290, Folder 15)
      - Swaziland
        - Lukhele, Thembi--USA# 261 (Box Box 290, Folder 16)
        - Ndiziba, Mrs. Bernice Sibongile--USA# 152 (Box Box 290, Folder 17)
        - Tshabalala, Collins--USA# 157 (Box Box 290, Folder 18)
      - Uganda
        - Buteera-Gawera (Box Box 290, Folder 19)
        - Guma, Paul--USA# 210 (Box Box 290, Folder 20)
        - Kaggwa, Livingstone--USA# 345 (Box Box 290, Folder 21)
        - Karuhanga, Ssam Rutehenda--USA# 223 (Box Box 290, Folder 22)
        - Kirenzi, Fred--USA# 39 (Box Box 290, Folder 23)
        - Kiyombo-Mayeku (Box Box 290, Folder 24)
        - Maumbe-Mukwana, Jack--USA# 76 (Box Box 290, Folder 25)
        - Mushanga-Rukubya (Box Box 290, Folder 26)
        - Sserunjogi-Yigga (Box Box 290, Folder 27)
      - Upper Volta
        - Tapsoba-Traore (Box Box 290, Folder 28)
        - Kanku ex-Remy--USA# 176 (Box Box 290, Folder 29)
      - Zaire
        - Kalamba, Kasala--USA# 153 (Box Box 290, Folder 30)
        - Kinkanda, Mahele--USA# 27 (Box Box 290, Folder 31)
        - Zamabi, Kuba Nkodya--USA# 207 (Box Box 290, Folder 32)
        - Case Closure Notices (Box Box 290, Folder 33)
      - Zimbabwe (Rhodesia)
        - Garwe, Forbes--USA# 28 (Box Box 290, Folder 34)
        - Gatsi-Gurure (Box Box 290, Folder 35)
        - Gwature, Timothy--USA# 38 (Box Box 290, Folder 36)
        - Gwitira, Mwaandudza Samson Mutisi--USA# 24 (Box Box 290, Folder 37)
        - Kanengoni-Madzimure (Box Box 290, Folder 38)
        - Mafemera, Michael--USA# 25 (Box Box 290, Folder 39)
        - Makazvarwa, Stanley M.--USA# 21 (Box Box 290, Folder 40)
        - Manduna-Mashila (Box Box 290, Folder 41)
        - Moyo, Michael Bhembe--USA# 43 (Box Box 290, Folder 42)
        - Moyo, Neviel Makazvuara--USA# 20 (Box Box 290, Folder 43)
        - Mudzindiko, Josephat--USA# 37 (Box Box 290, Folder 44)
        - Munyanyi, Clever Claudius--USA# 97 (Box Box 290, Folder 45)
        - Nyamuraradza-Nyonii (Box Box 291, Folder 1)
        - Sibanda (Box Box 291, Folder 2)
        - Sipanera-Sithole (Box Box 291, Folder 3)
    - Americas
      - Argentina
        - Arabaolasa-Aybar (Box Box 291, Folder 4)
        - Asbat, Enrique Asbat (Box Box 291, Folder 5)
        - Beltramino de Loto, Maria de las Experanzas--USA #100 (Box Box 291, Folder 6)
        - Elizaga, Hugo Raul--USA #175 (Box Box 291, Folder 7)
        - Foresti, Norberto Hugo--USA# 38 (Box Box 291, Folder 8)
        - Gasparini, Osvaldo--USA# 110 (Box Box 291, Folder 9)
        - Martinez-Pozzo (Box Box 291, Folder 10)
        - Reyes-Rios (Box Box 291, Folder 11)
        - Romero-Tripoli (Box Box 291, Folder 12)
        - Unfiled/Loose Case Closure Notices (Box Box 291, Folder 13)
      - Chile
        - Vila, Carlos Lopez--USA# 159 (Box Box 291, Folder 14)
        - Unfiled/Loose Case Closure Notices (Box Box 291, Folder 15)
      - Colombia
        - Agudelo, Sneider--USA# 148 (Box Box 291, Folder 16)
        - Chamorro (Box Box 291, Folder 17)
      - Cuba
        - Gonzalez, Justino Ramos--USA# 237 (Box Box 291, Folder 18)
        - Rodriguez, Jose Agustin Lopez--USA# 211 (Box Box 291, Folder 19)
      - El Salvador
        - Euceda-Mejia (Box Box 291, Folder 20)
        - Melendez-Varela (Box Box 291, Folder 21)
      - Grenada
        - Bartholomew, Sydney--USA# 193 (Box Box 291, Folder 22)
        - Unfiled/Loose Case Closure Notices (Box Box 291, Folder 23)
      - Haiti-- Antoine-Theodore (Box Box 291, Folder 24)
      - Mexico--Gonzalez-Jesus (Box Box 291, Folder 25)
      - Paraguay
        - Acosta, Ramon Paiva--USA# 192 (Box Box 291, Folder 26)
        - Alegre-Davalos (Box Box 291, Folder 27)
        - Esquivel-Sevilla (Box Box 291, Folder 28)
        - Case Closure Notices (Box Box 291, Folder 29)
      - Peru--Huaman-Rojas (Box Box 291, Folder 30)
      - Trinidad/Tobago--Death Penalty Dossier--USA# 3/16 (Box Box 291, Folder 31)
      - Uruguay
        - Acosta, Carlos Cunha--USA# 197 (Box Box 291, Folder 32)
        - Aldrovandi, Pedro--USA#212 (Box Box 291, Folder 33)
        - Almada-Barreix (Box Box 291, Folder 34)
        - Bas, Juan Manuel Rodriguez--USA# 118 (Box Box 291, Folder 35)
        - Batalla-Besio (Box Box 291, Folder 36)
        - Buffa, Miguel Angel Muyala--USA#88 (Box Box 291, Folder 37)
        - Carballo-Crespo (Box Box 291, Folder 38)
        - Croki-De Leon (Box Box 291, Folder 39)
        - Diaz, Juan Jose Alonzo--USA# 127 (Box Box 291, Folder 40)
        - Esponda, Pedro Humberto Varela--USA# 190 (Box Box 291, Folder 41)
        - Fernandez-Ferreira (Box Box 291, Folder 42)
        - Ferriero, Daniel--USA# 70 (Box Box 291, Folder 43)
        - Frustacio, Jose Luis--USA# 37 (Box Box 291, Folder 44)
        - Fuentes-Garrido (Box Box 291, Folder 45)
        - Gimenez, Tomas Stala--USA# 181 (Box Box 291, Folder 46)
        - Gonzalez (Box Box 291, Folder 47)
        - Gonazalez-Haflinger (Box Box 291, Folder 48)
        - Klivsov-Kuzawka (Box Box 291, Folder 49)
        - Lara, Nestor Ramilo--USA# 5 (Box Box 291, Folder 50)
        - Lawlor-Lev (Box Box 291, Folder 51)
        - Machado-Mena (Box Box 291, Folder 52)
        - Mendez-Monroy (Box Box 292, Folder 1)
        - Morena, Juan Antonio D’Albora--USA# 23 (Box Box 292, Folder 2)
        - Orlando, Juan Antonio Rodriguez--USA # 180 (Box Box 292, Folder 3)
        - Ormarchea-Oxley (Box Box 292, Folder 4)
        - Paita, Gladys--USA# 63 (Box Box 292, Folder 5)
        - Perdomo, Reuben--USA# 103 (Box Box 292, Folder 6)
        - Pons, Francisco Laurenzo--USA# 16 (Box Box 292, Folder 7)
        - Quijano, Rodriguez (Box Box 292, Folder 8)
        - Rodriguez, Alvaro Rodriguez--USA# 173 (Box Box 292, Folder 9)
        - Romerao-Sabasky (Box Box 292, Folder 10)
        - Sanchez, Maria Julia Minvielle--USA# 172 (Box Box 292, Folder 11)
        - Skriller, Juan Solarich--USA# 125 (Box Box 292, Folder 12)
        - Soca, Juan Carlos Sanchez--USA# 50 (Box Box 292, Folder 13)
        - Trelles, Dr. Gualberto--USA# 59 (Box Box 292, Folder 14)
        - Vaz, Yolanda Esponda--USA# 50 (Box Box 292, Folder 15)
        - Villaverde-Zarfino (Box Box 292, Folder 16)
        - Unfiled/Loose Case Closure Notices and Case Reports (Box Box 292, Folder 17)
      - Venezuela--Beltran, Nicolas Montes--USA# 44 (Box Box 292, Folder 18)
    - Asia
      - Bangladesh
        - Ahmed, Khandakar Mushtaque--USA# 44 (Box Box 292, Folder 19)
        - Ali-De (Box Box 292, Folder 20)
        - Jehad, Nasiruddin--USA # 263 (Box Box 292, Folder 21)
        - Mazed, Golam--USA #2 (Includes unfiled case closure notices for other cases) (Box Box 292, Folder 22)
      - China
        - Liu, Jafa --USA# 47 (Box Box 292, Folder 23)
        - Tao, Sen--USA# 3/16 (Box Box 292, Folder 24)
        - Wei, Yuehua--USA# 156 (Includes unfiled case closure notices for other cases) (Box Box 292, Folder 25)
      - India--Gonja-Singh (Box Box 292, Folder 26)
      - Indonesia
        - Aidit, Dr. Sutanti--USA# 11 (Box Box 292, Folder 27)
        - Hartati, Ms. Tati--USA# 77 (Box Box 292, Folder 28)
        - Helmi-Sugiono (Box Box 292, Folder 29)
        - Sujatno, Sgt. Anis (Box Box 292, Folder 30)
        - Tewa, Anton--USA# 32 (Includes unfiled case closure notices for other cases) (Box Box 292, Folder 31)
      - Malaysia--Sang, Tan Thean--USA# 70 (Includes unfiled case closure notices for other cases) (Box Box 292, Folder 32)
      - Nepal--Thulung, Baburam--USA# 100 (Includes unfiled case closure notices for other cases) (Box Box 292, Folder 33)
      - Pakistan
        - Abbas-Ahmed (Box Box 292, Folder 34)
        - Bibi-Mohammad (Box Box 292, Folder 35)
        - Mohammad-Zubaida (Box Box 292, Folder 36)
        - Unfiled/Loose Case Closure Notices (Box Box 292, Folder 37)
      - Philippines
        - Astudillo-Caudillo (Box Box 292, Folder 38)
        - Carino-Corro (Box Box 292, Folder 39)
        - Gaspar-Holganza (Box Box 292, Folder 40)
        - Lucero, Father Peter (Box Box 292, Folder 41)
        - Mangao-Rebullido (Box Box 292, Folder 42)
        - Royas-Santos (Box Box 294, Folder 1)
        - Soriano-Vistro (Box Box 294, Folder 2)
      - Singapore--Teng-Zahari (Box Box 294, Folder 3)
      - South Korea
        - Ahn-Ehaw Women’s University (Box Box 294, Folder 4)
        - Hwang, Hyong-Sung (Box Box 294, Folder 5)
        - Kim-Koh (Box Box 294, Folder 6)
        - Lee (Box Box 294, Folder 7)
        - Pae, Yong-Sik--USA# 9 (Box Box 294, Folder 8)
        - Pang-Sohn (Box Box 294, Folder 9)
        - Song-Yonsei University (Box Box 294, Folder 10)
      - Sri Lanka
        - Chandrasiri-Dharmasekera (Box Box 294, Folder 11)
        - Kulasegararajasingham, Chelliah--USA# 71 (Box Box 294, Folder 12)
        - Manasan-Uthayakumar (Box Box 294, Folder 13)
      - Taiwan
        - Chang-Chen (Box Box 294, Folder 14)
        - Chen (Box Box 294, Folder 15)
        - Hsu-Hung (Box Box 294, Folder 16)
        - Hung-Li (Box Box 294, Folder 17)
        - Li, Ching-sun--USA# 1 (Box Box 294, Folder 18)
        - Li-Lin (Box Box 294, Folder 19)
        - Lin-Liu (Box Box 294, Folder 20)
        - Liu-Tai (Box Box 294, Folder 21)
        - Tsai, Yu-Jung--USA# 169 (Box Box 294, Folder 22)
        - Tseng, Cheng-chin--USA# 67 (Box Box 294, Folder 23)
        - Wang-Yen and Unfiled Case Closure Notices (Box Box 294, Folder 24)
      - Thailand
        - Arphornram-Boonpeng (Box Box 294, Folder 25)
        - Te-rin, Virunthana--USA# 96 (Box Box 294, Folder 26)
        - Unrat-Uttaphan (Box Box 294, Folder 27)
      - Vietnam--Dong, Nguyen--USA# 4 (Box Box 294, Folder 28)
    - Europe
      - Bulgaria--Koleu-Spasou (Box Box 294, Folder 29)
      - Czechoslovakia
        - Battek, Rudolf--USA# 3/16 (Box Box 294, Folder 30)
        - Cerny, Miloslav--USA# 19 (Box Box 294, Folder 31)
        - Duray, Miklos--USA# 311 (Box Box 294, Folder 32)
        - Merganz-Panecek (Box Box 294, Folder 33)
        - Sabara, Professor Jaroslav--USA# 6 (Box Box 294, Folder 34)
        - Savrda-Vyhnalek (Box Box 294, Folder 35)
      - France--Fraizy, Jean-Luc--USA# 76 (Box Box 294, Folder 36)
      - East Germany
        - Bederke-Eichwede (Box Box 294, Folder 37)
        - Fischer, Frank and Christa--USA #279 (Box Box 294, Folder 38)
        - Fliegner-Hentschel (Box Box 294, Folder 39)
        - Holfman, Leoni--USA# 33 (Box Box 294, Folder 40)
        - Jursch-Krack (Box Box 294, Folder 41)
        - Kuhnigk-Kupris (Box Box 294, Folder 42)
        - Lehmann, Egbert and Karla--USA# 9 (Box Box 295, Folder 1)
        - Lesniak-Linde (Box Box 295, Folder 2)
        - Lindenthal, Waldeman and Ingrid--USA# 147 (Box Box 295, Folder 3)
        - Loos-Schadwald (Box Box 295, Folder 4)
        - Scheithauer-Simon (Box Box 295, Folder 5)
        - Stock-Wegner (Box Box 295, Folder 6)
        - Wilhelm, Manred--USA# 135 (Box Box 295, Folder 7)
        - Unfiled/Loose Case Closure Notices (Box Box 295, Folder 8)
      - Greece
        - Boviatsos-Konstantinidis (Box Box 295, Folder 9)
        - Kostoulias, Miltiades--USA# 63 (Box Box 295, Folder 10)
        - Krokos-Makris (Box Box 295, Folder 11)
        - Petrakis, Yannis--USA# 346 (Box Box 295, Folder 12)
        - Sterioglou-Tsialas (Box Box 295, Folder 13)
      - Italy--Capuzzo-Turolla (Box Box 295, Folder 14)
      - Poland
        - Glebocki-Kalemba (Box Box 295, Folder 15)
        - Kolodzieg, Stanislaw--USA# 28 (Box Box 295, Folder 16)
        - Tulasz, Chrystoforosz (Box Box 295, Folder 17)
        - Zajac, Rudolf--USA# 49 and Unfiled Case Closure Notices for Other Cases (Box Box 295, Folder 18)
      - Romania
        - Andreescu-Condrut (Box Box 295, Folder 19)
        - Calciu, Father Gheroghe (Box Box 295, Folder 20)
        - Fackner-Papp (Box Box 295, Folder 21)
        - Popescu, Carmen--USA# 253 (Box Box 295, Folder 22)
        - Preda-Tarnisceru (Box Box 295, Folder 23)
      - Spain--Pena, Mauel Carlos Sorli--USA# 182 (Box Box 295, Folder 24)
      - Switzerland--Gros, Thierry--USA# 149 (Box Box 295, Folder 25)
      - Turkey
        - Aydin-Kilic (Box Box 295, Folder 26)
        - Kizmaz, Ayse--USa# 48 (Box Box 295, Folder 27)
        - Kucukuysal-Oflaz (Box Box 295, Folder 28)